

FISNIK MURATI

Fullstack Developer

+383 49 253 853



fisnikmurati94@gmail.com



Kosova, Prishtine



ABOUT ME

Motivated Web Developer with an extensive knowledge of web development, design, and coding, as well as experience in a wide range of programming languages, frameworks, and tools. Proven success in developing and deploying applications, websites, and web services. Highly organized and detail-oriented, with a knack for finding creative solutions to challenging problems.

EDUCATION

Gymnasium -High School

2015 - 2018

Bachelor of Science In Informatics

2019-2021

SKILLS

- Strong organizational and timemanagement skills
- Exceptional communication and interpersonal skills
- Ability to work independently and as part of a team
- Detail-oriented and able to handle multiple tasks simultaneously
- Knowledge on: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript(VueJs, ReactJs), PHP(Symfony, Laravel), Database(MySql, SqlServer, MongoDb).

LANGUAGE

- Albanian
- English

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Ajroni Web Agency

Remote | 2022 - Present

- Working with Laravel VueJs as Fullstack Developer, also testing and QA.
- Coordinate and schedule meetings and conferences with internal and external stakeholders.

E-Solution

Office | 2019 - 2022

 Working with Laravel - VueJs as Fullstack Developer, also testing and QA.

Freelance

Office | 2017 - 2019

• Working with Laravel - VueJs as Fullstack Developer, also testing and QA.